<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Streak</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pipeline">Pipeline</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_mail">Why Hire Me</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        <b>Hello!</b>\n
        The following Android App showcases my ability as an Android developer and UI/UX designer.
        My expertise in this field ensures the creation of a beautiful and functional app.
        I have extensive experience in fast paced environments that require efficient development methodologies.
        The following projects bring light to the various apps I have created.
    </string>


    <string name="virus">
        First place for Cisco at SBHacks. Virus is a fast-paced collective game of zombie tag.
        A certain amount of people in the network are infected.
        Their goal is to run around and tag healthy people by getting in a close proximity to them. If you get tagged, you are now infected as well.
        Features include real-time Wi-Fi tracking within 4ft, massive scalability of users, and real-time database. 
    </string>

    <string name="storify">
        Crowd Favorite Award at Cutie Hacks. Storify allows users to anonymously finish each other\'s stories.
        You start your first sentence and another person continues it, and so on so forth.
        \n
    </string>

     <string name="smartgym">
        First Place for AngelHacks. Smart Gym is an IoT device that automatically tracks workouts
        The app showcases real time data, uses accelerometer to count reps, and builds workouts
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="title_smartgym"><a href="http://devpost.com/software/smart-machine"><b>Smart Gym</b></a>\n</string>

    <string name="title_storify"><a href="http://devpost.com/software/storify"><b>Storify</b></a>\n</string>

    <string name="title_virus"><a href="http://sbhacks.devpost.com/submissions/32408-virus"><b>Virus</b></a>\n</string>




</resources>
